{
  "quiz": {
    "questionItem": [
      {
        "question": "Which does jQuery use as a shortcut for jQuery?",
        "panswer": [
          "the % sign",
          "the ? Sign",
          "the $ sign",
          "the jQ sign"
        ],
        "aanswer": "the $ sign"
      },
      {
        "question": "With jQuery, look at the following selector: $('div'). What does it select?",
        "panswer": [
          "All div elements",
          "The first div element",
          "The last div element",
          "nothing"
        ],
        "aanswer": "All div elements"
      },
      {
        "question": "jQuery is a library for:",
        "panswer": [
          "home scripting",
          "server scripting",
          "TPS scripting",
          "client scripting"
        ],
        "aanswer": "client scripting"
      },
      {
        "question": "What code sets all 'p' elements background color to red?",
        "panswer": [
          "$('p').css('background-color','red');",
          "$('p').style('background-color','red');",
          "$('p').layout('background-color','red');",
          "$('p').manipulate('background-color','red');"
        ],
        "aanswer": "$('p').css('background-color','red');"
      },
      {
        "question": "With jQuery, look at the following selector: $('div.intro'). What does it select?",
        "panswer": [
          "All div elements with class='intro'",
          "The first div element with class='intro'",
          "All div elements with id='intro'",
          "The first div element with id='intro'"
        ],
        "aanswer": "All div elements with class='intro'"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which jQuery method is used to hide selected elements?",
        "panswer": [
          "visible(false)",
          "hidden()",
          "hide()",
          "display(none)"
        ],
        "aanswer": "hide()"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which jQuery method is used to set one or more style properties for selected elements?",
        "panswer": [
          "html()",
          "style()",
          "css()",
          "styles()"
        ],
        "aanswer": "css()"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which jQuery method is used to perform an asynchronous HTTP request?",
        "panswer": [
          "jQuery.ajax()",
          "jQuery.ajaxAsync()",
          "jQuery.ajaxSetup()",
          "jQuery.AJAX()"
        ],
        "aanswer": "jQuery.ajax()"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the correct jQuery code for making all div elements 100 pixels high?",
        "panswer": [
          "$('div').yPos(100)",
          "$('div').height(100)",
          "$('div').height='100'",
          "$('div').xPos(100)"
        ],
        "aanswer": "$('div').height(100)"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which is true:",
        "panswer": [
          "To use jQuery, you do not have to do anything. Most browsers (Internet Explorer, Chrome, Firefox and Opera) have the jQuery library built in the browser",
          "To use jQuery, you can refer to a hosted jQuery library at Google",
          "To use jQuery, you must buy the jQuery library at www.jquery.com",
          "jQuery is built into core Javascript"
        ],
        "aanswer": "To use jQuery, you can refer to a hosted jQuery library at Google"
      },
      {
        "question": "What scripting language is jQuery written in?",
        "panswer": [
          "Javascript",
          "C#",
          "C++",
          "VBScript"
        ],
        "aanswer": "Javascript"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which jQuery function is used to prevent code from running, before the document is finished loading?",
        "panswer": [
          "$(document).load()",
          "$(document).ready()",
          "$(body).onload()",
          "$(body).ready()"
        ],
        "aanswer": "$(document).ready()"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which jQuery method should be used to deal with name conflicts?",
        "panswer": [
          "conflict()",
          "noConflict()",
          "noNameConflict()",
          "nameConflict()"
        ],
        "aanswer": "noConflict()"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which jQuery method is used to switch between adding/removing one or more classes (for CSS) from selected elements?",
        "panswer": [
          "switch()",
          "switchClass()",
          "toggleClass()",
          "altClass()"
        ],
        "aanswer": "toggleClass()"
      },
      {
        "question": "Look at the following jQuery selector: $('div#intro .head'). What does it select?",
        "panswer": [
          "All div elements with id='intro' or class='head'",
          "All elements with class='head' inside the first div element with id='intro'",
          "The first element with id='head' inside any div element with class='intro'",
          "All div elements with a parent of 'head'"
        ],
        "aanswer": "All elements with class='head' inside the first div element with id='intro'"
      }
    ]
  }
}